http://www.luggageonline.com/customer-service/privacy-security

Luggage
Travel
Blog
SIGN UP AND SAVE 20%* OFF TODAY!
Luggage Online
0 items in cart.
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search Site
Search:
Search
Luggage.
All Brands
Business.
All Brands
Duffels.
All Brands
Backpacks.
Popular Brands
Herschel Supply Co.
All Brands
Messenger Bags.
All Brands
Handbags.
All Brands
Kids.
All Brands
Adventure.
All Brands
Accessories.
Baggallini
Brands.
Hartmann
Herschel Supply Co.
ZERO Halliburton
SALE.
Menu
Luggage.
All Brands
Business.
All Brands
Duffels.
All Brands
Backpacks.
Popular Brands
Herschel Supply Co.
All Brands
Messenger Bags.
All Brands
Handbags.
All Brands
Kids.
All Brands
Adventure.
All Brands
Accessories.
Baggallini
Brands.
Hartmann
Herschel Supply Co.
ZERO Halliburton
SALE.
No Thanks, I don't like to save money
You did not add any gift products to the cart. Check your available gifts!
Privacy Policy
Luggage Online is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal information you provide online. We've provided this notice to explain how we collect and use and your personal information. If you have any questions regarding this policy, you may direct them to customerservice@luggageonline.com.
What information do we collect? How do we use it? We use your personal information solely to help us service your account, to improve our services to you, to provide you with the products you have requested, and to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you. We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive.
Will Luggage Online disclose the information it collects to outside parties? Luggage Online will never sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
How does Luggage Online use cookies? "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide tailored information from our web site and store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can change the settings in your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
A special note concerning children’s privacy. The safety of children is obviously very important to us. Children should always ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. Luggage Online does not knowingly collect or maintain information at our website from those who are under 18.
Is there anything else I should know? Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In addition, the privacy policies of other websites will vary, while many will have no stated privacy policy.
In short, if you provide personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. It is ultimately your responsibility to maintain the secrecy of your personal information to the extent you feel comfortable. We encourage you to be careful and to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.
Your Consent By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Luggage Online. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Security Policy
How does Luggage Online protect customer information? When you place an order or access your account information, our servers use Secure Sockets Layers (SSL). SSL encrypts, or scrambles, your information while in transit to us, and it can only be decrypted, or unscrambled, by an authorized computer. Furthermore, all the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
If you choose to pay using a credit card, Luggage Online or any of its employees do not store or have any type of access to credit card information.
Credit card details are encrypted and securely stored by a third party company, Authorize.net. Authorize.Net and its parent company, CyberSource, validate security measures against applicable sections of numerous federal and state laws – HIPAA, GLBA, California Seate Bill 1386 (SB1386), and many others.
You may find a copy of Authorize.net security policy in the following link: http://www.authorize.net/solutions/merchantsolutions/merchantservices/security/
How to Contact Us Should you have other questions or concerns about these policies, please send us an e-mail to customerservice@lugaggeonline.com.
Pricing & Discount Policies
Items in your Shopping Cart will always reflect the most recent prices displayed on the items' product detail page, the daily promotion and any coupon code you entered. Please note this price may differ from the prices shown for the items when you first placed them in your Shopping Cart. Placing an item in your Shopping Cart does not necessarily reserve the price shown at that time; most Luggage Online discount offers are for a limited time only, and have stated expiration dates. Accordingly, it is possible that an item's price may change between the time you place it in your Shopping Cart and the time you complete your Checkout. In addition, prices are subject to availability of the product at the time of ordering.
While Luggage Online strives to provide accurate pricing information, pricing or typographical errors may occur. Luggage Online cannot confirm the price of an item until after you order. In the event that an item is listed at an incorrect price due to an error in pricing, Luggage Online shall have the right, at Luggage Online's sole discretion, to refuse or cancel any orders placed for that item. In the event that an item is mispriced, Luggage Online may, at Luggage Online’s sole discretion, either contact you for instructions or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation.
Please note that this policy applies only to products sold and shipped by LuggageOnline.com. Luggage Online regrets that we cannot be responsible for pricing errors made on third-party or affiliated web sites, or prices quoted incorrectly in print publications which are not directly affiliated with Luggage Online.
At Luggage Online, Free Shipping, Percent Savings and Dollar Savings are all considered to be promotional offers. Coupons and discounts apply only to available inventory and your next purchase. We're sorry, but we do not offer rain checks. Coupons and discounts may not be combined with other coupons or discounts. Coupons and discounts may not be applied to the purchase of E-Gift Cards or to Luggage Online corporate sales orders. We're sorry, but some discounts are not applicable to certain brands or collections.
To be sure you get the best deal, we provide a 110% Low-Price Guarantee. If you find a product for less from an authorized website, contact us before making the purchase and we’ll give you 110% of the difference. It’s that simple! Competitor's shipping charges, if any, will be included. Offer valid on Internet advertised prices only. Items must be in stock on our site as well as our competitor’s, and the item must be exactly the same including its color. Price guarantee not valid on auction sites, shopping comparison sites, international websites, discounters, Amazon.com, Ebay,com, Walmart.com or for items that are improperly priced against manufacturers pricing and discount guidelines. Price guarantee does not apply to orders that have already been placed.
At Luggage Online, Free Shipping, Percent Savings and Dollar Savings are all considered to be promotional offers. Coupons and discounts apply only to available inventory and your next purchase. We're sorry, but we do not offer rain checks. Coupons and discounts may not be combined with other coupons or discounts. Coupons and discounts may not be applied to the purchase of E-Gift Cards or to Luggage Online corporate sales orders.
We're sorry, but some discounts are not applicable to certain brands or collections.
PROMOTIONS:
Luggage Online is happy to offer special promotions every week.
Each Deal including our first time Insider signup code is subject to brand exclusions unless otherwise stated in marketing materials posted on our homepage. Luggage Online reserves the right to modify or cancel this offer at any time. Up to savings message reflects MSRP, not list price. Free Shipping valid on US orders only. Discounts do not apply toward the purchase of gift certificates.
Excluded Brands from all promotions include:
*Rimowa
*Bric's
*Briggs & Riley
*Bosca
*Eagle Creek
*Timbuk2
*Any item already on sale
Return Policy
Return Policy - Your satisfaction is GUARANTEED! All Luggage Online products come with our 30-day Easy Returns policy. If, for any reason, you not satisfied with your purchase, simply contact us within 30 days from the delivery date of the item to obtain a Return Merchandise Authorization number (RMA). If the item is not received back within 10 business days from RMA date, your return will not be valid and your RMA will be closed. Once item is returned, you will receive a full refund of the original price of the product.
Details
All merchandise must be in the same new, unused condition in which you received them.
Items returned to Luggage Online that are not in new, unused condition will be on hold until  customer send a call tag and no refund will be made.
Returns will not be valid without an RMA number emailed to you. To obtain an RMA number, please call (844) 999-7678 or email customerservice@luggageonline.com. Please include a copy of your RMA email with your returned merchandise.
In the case of returns, all customers are expected to cover the cost of return shipping. For your protection we recommended that you use a traceable and insurable form of shipment for your return, such as FedEx or UPS. Please ship your package to the address listed below.
Once your return is received and inspected by Luggage Online, your card will be credited the original price of the product and any applicable taxes. Any original shipping fees are not refundable.
Credits will be issued by Luggage Online within 3 to 4 business days from when we receive your returned product(s). Credit card companies vary on the time it takes for credit to appear on their customers' records. Please allow 7-10 business days for the credit to appear on your statement.
All Final Sales are non-returnable. All personalized or monogrammed items are non-returnable.
FREE EXCHANGES
If you would like to exchange your item for something that better fits your needs, we can take care of that for you free of charge within 30 days of the delivery date.  Simply follow the same process and details that are outlined above, but in addition to receiving an RMA number you will also receive a PRE-PAID UPS label that you can use to return the item you’d like to exchange. Please note that the prepaid label will only be provided when exchanging for an item of greater value, when exchanging for lesser value a prepaid label will not be provided. However, all customers are limited to one (1) exchange per order. Whichever item you choose in the exchange will be considered FINAL SALE and is non-returnable or exchangeable. All exchanges are shipped via UPS Ground (No Expedited Shipping).
Exchange Procedure
Request RMA number & Pre-Paid UPS Label.
Print RMA email and place it inside the item box (All items should be returned in NEW conditions, with tags, and in original packaging).
Print PRE-PAID UPS label, attach it to outside of box, and drop it off at your nearest UPS location.
Once the item is received and inspected by Luggage Online, we will issue a STORE CREDIT to your Luggage Online account for the amount paid for the item.
Place an order for the item you would like in exchange and use the store credit towards that purchase.
Complete the order and patiently wait for the exchange to be processed and shipped.
Please note that any store credit given is non-refundable.
Shipping Address for Returns & Exchanges
Please include a copy of your RMA email and send all Returns and Exchanges to:
Luggage Online
Returns Department
260 Liberty St.
Metuchen, NJ 08840
Additional Details
Luggage Online does not accept returns on personalized merchandise
All products must be returned unused, in their original box and packaging
Lump sum promotional discounts (e.g. $20 off your order) will be distributed across all applicable products. Credit amounts for returns / exchanges will be based on this discounted price
Items that included a GWP (gift with purchase) that are returned must be accompanied with the GWP item or the advertised value of the GWP will be withheld from the credited amount
Items sold at a promotional price must be returned, if not, we will deduct the amount discounted to credit
Defective or Damaged Good
Please contact us immediately if your Luggage Online purchase arrives in defective or damaged condition. Items that arrive in defective* or damaged condition will be replaced immediately.
*Defective merchandise is covered for 30 days by Luggage Online. After that time please refer to the manufacturer for warranty service.
Customer Service
Contact Us
FAQs
Judging Quality
Products
Ordering
Shipping
Airline Damaged Luggage
Redeeming E-Gift Cards
Problems with a E-Gift Card?
E-Gift Cards Terms & Conditions
Shipping
Domestic Rates
International Shipping
Estimate Shipping Time
Shipping to AK, HI & PR
Rimowa Shipping Upgrade
Returns
Shopping
Product Information Product Videos Corporate Orders Ratings & Reviews Policies
E-Gift Card
Learn More
Customer Service
Contact Us
Help Center
My Account
Returns / RMA
Check Order Status
FAQs
Services
Live Chat
"
About us
About us
Affiliate Program
Site Map
Rewards Program
Enjoy savings by earning purchase points through our customer rewards program.
Learn More
SIGN UP AND SAVE 20%* OFF TODAY!
Luggage Online is the premier online source for all your luggage and travel accessory needs.Our extensive inventory carries everything from backpacks and briefcases to multi-piece luggage sets for the whole family.
© 2020 LuggageOnline.com All Rights Reserved
Live Chat
The Quickest way to get help.
Chat with a customer care agent
Call Us Toll Free 1-844-999-7678
Monday - Friday 9:00 a.m. - 6:00 p.m. EST
Email
Send us an email to customerservice@luggageonline.com. We will reply promptly within one business day.
Email your question or comment
Customer Help Center
Find information on Customer Service topics like how to place or track an order, how to return an item, and how to manage your luggageonline account.
Visit our Customer Help Center
Luggage Online HQ Offices
260 Liberty st.
Metuchen, NJ 08840
customerservice@luggageonline.com
Bolt Checkout
Sorry, but something went wrong. Please contact the seller.
Close
x
Back to top
